var cardsGreen = [];

var cardsRed = [];


cardsGreen.push({
			question:'Butts?',

			options:[

					'Yes',

					'No',

					'Myabe',

					'Can\'t see.',

		],
			correct:1

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'Where is the rebel base?',

			options:[

					'Alderaan',

					'Hoth',

					'Mars',

					'Your mom\'s place',

		],
			correct:2

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'DROP TABLE;'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'DROP DATABASE ;'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'apweiofhawe[fijkaw]epojcawoeifawpoiejfawpojfa[oweifjaw[oeifjaw[oeifjaw[oeifjaw[eofijawe\'[oifjaw[eofijaw[eofijaw[eofijaw[eoifjawe[oifjaw[\'eofjaw[eofija[fgoijsd;fogvjnsefoiuawefopkjaw]efojser[guheafokawe[\'ofiahr[gfoiuawjfa\'[woiefj[awoeijfa[weoigfjseprihgaepliufhawepifuhawpeiufhaweiofhawepoifja[wijfapweoifjawpoeifjaw[eoifja[oweifjapweoifjapweoifjawpoeuifhaprgiuhaw[oiefja[weoifjaweiojfawpoeifjapwoeifjap[oigha[weoifhawpioeuhga[woidja[woeifja[weoifja[woeifjaw[eoifjaw[eoifjaw[oeifjaw[eofihaw[eoiuhaw[oeihg'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'''+w'
	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'How many roads must a man walk down?',

			options:[

					'69',

					'42',

					'53',

					'Is this a Bob Dylan reference?',

		],
			correct:2

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'How many sidewalks must a man walk down?',

			options:[

					'Fuck off.',

					'3',

					'4',

					'32',

		],
			correct:3

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'Tell about a time you saw David Bromberg live.'
	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'What color is absinthe?',

			options:[

					'Blue',

					'Green',

					'Yellow',

					'Red',

		],
			correct:2

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'Tell me about the time you had an ethics complex with your coworkers? Use lots of unnecessary language and be as confusing as possible'
	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'Who averaged a patent for every three weeks of his life?',

			options:[

					'Benjamin Franklin',

					'Isaac Newton',

					'Thomas Edison',

					'John Newton',

		],
			correct:3

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'What is the alcohol per volume of Sierra Nevada Pale Ale?',

			options:[

					'4.5%',

					'6.3%',

					'4.2%',

					'5.6%',

		],
			correct:4

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'How many beers does it take to get Griffin drunk?',

			options:[

					'6',

					'9',

					'10',

					'As many beers it takes to get Griffin drunk.',

		],
			correct:4

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'If you were to run for your local school board, why would you not get elected?'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'What was the worst Christmas you ever had?'
	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'How many Christmas?',

			options:[

					'Enough',

					'Eight menora candles',

					'Qwelve',

					'6',

		],
			correct:1

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'How many times have you eaten?'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'How did you cause the apocolypse?'
	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'How many molecules are on Leonard Nimoy\'s butt?'
	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'Why?',

			options:[

					'How?',

					'Yes.',

					'Because.',

					'Well I never.',

		],
			correct:3

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'How do you spell protein?',

			options:[

					'Protein',

					'Protein',

					'Protein',

					'Protein',

		],
			correct:1

	});

cardsGreen.push({
			question:'What color is my shirt?',

			options:[

					'White',

					'Indeterminate',

					'Green',

					'Fart',

		],
			correct:2

	});

cardsRed.push({
			question:'What was the last thing you said to a dog?'
	});

